{
    "subject": "resource/Bruce_Willis",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Walter Bruce Willis (born March 19, 1955) is an American actor, producer and singer. His career began on the Off-Broadway stage and then in television in the 1980s, most notably as David Addison in Moonlighting (1985\u201389). He is perhaps best known for his role of John McClane in the Die Hard series, which were mostly critical and uniformly financial successes.  He has appeared in over sixty films, including Color of Night (1994), Pulp Fiction (1994), 12 Monkeys (1995), The Fifth Element (1997), Armageddon (1998), The Sixth Sense (1999), Unbreakable (2000), Sin City (2005), Red (2010) and The Expendables 2 (2012).Motion pictures featuring Willis have grossed US$2.64 billion to $3.05 billion at North American box offices, making him the eighth highest-grossing actor in a leading role and 12th-highest including supporting roles. He is a two-time Emmy Award\u2013winning, Golden Globe Award\u2013winning and four-time Saturn Award\u2013nominated actor. Willis was married to actress Demi Moore and they had three daughters before their divorce in 2000, following thirteen years of marriage. Since 2009, he has been married to model Emma Heming, with whom he has two daughters.",
    "human_readable": "The abstract of Bruce Willis is Walter Bruce Willis (born March 19, 1955) is an American actor, producer and singer.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8987385630607605,
            "question": "Is Bruce Willis American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8564980030059814,
            "question": "When was Bruce Willis born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8393362760543823,
            "question": "What year was Bruce Willis born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7083618640899658,
            "question": "What month was Bruce Willis born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.672467052936554,
            "question": "What nationality is Bruce Willis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6612292528152466,
            "question": "What is Bruce Willis's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6118096709251404,
            "question": "What is Bruce Willis best known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5700491070747375,
            "question": "Besides acting, what other profession does Bruce Willis have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5318198800086975,
            "question": "What are some of Bruce Willis's professions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40499264001846313,
            "question": "Does Bruce Willis have any musical talents?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The abstract of Bruce Willis is Walter Bruce Willis (born March 19, 1955) is an American actor, producer and singer.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7831_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Bruce Willis's professions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7831_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides acting, what other profession does Bruce Willis have?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7831_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Bruce Willis best known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7831_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7831_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7831_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7831_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7831_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7831_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7831_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7831_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7831_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7831_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7831_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text describes Bruce Willis as \"an American actor, producer, and singer\".  Additionally, it states that Walter Bruce Willis was born on March 19, 1955. This aligns with the abstract's description. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation:\n\nThe triple to be evaluated is: \"The abstract of Bruce Willis is Walter Bruce Willis (born March 19, 1955) is an American actor, producer and singer.\"\n\nBased on the provided context information, all the documents mention Bruce Willis as an American actor, producer, or musician. Therefore, the statement is supported by the documents.\n\nSo, the response should be:\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe provided abstracts from the documents all confirm that Walter Bruce Willis (born March 19, 1955) is indeed described as an American actor, producer, and singer. Therefore, the given triple is correct according to the context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}